{
  "data":{
    "quizTitle":"Sample Practice Test",
    "quizTotalQuestions": "",
    "quizDescription": "Good Sample quiz",
    "quizMetaTag": "GK, SAmple",
    "quizThumbNail": "",
    "quizId": "Sample",
    "quizLevel": "",
    "quizScore": "",
    "questions":[
      {
        "options":[
          "Justin",
          "Narendra",
          "Scott",
          "Mahesh"
        ],
        "questionImg":null,
        "questionId":0,
        "question":"Who?",
        "answer":2,
        "answerSelected":-1
      },
      {
        "options":[
          "Scott",
          "Justin",
          "Narendra",
          "Mahesh"
        ],
        "questionImg":null,
        "questionId":1,
        "question":"Who?",
        "answer":0,
        "answerSelected":-1
      },
      {
        "options":[
          "Narendra",
          "Justin",
          "Scott",
          "Mahesh"
        ],
        "questionImg":null,
        "questionId":2,
        "question":"Who?",
        "answer":2,
        "answerSelected":-1
      },
      {
        "options":[
          "Justin",
          "Narendra",
          "Scott",
          "Mahesh"
        ],
        "questionImg":null,
        "questionId":3,
        "question":"Who?",
        "answer":2,
        "answerSelected":-1
      },
      {
        "options":[
          "Scott",
          "Justin",
          "Narendra",
          "Mahesh"
        ],
        "questionImg":null,
        "questionId":4,
        "question":"Who?",
        "answer":0,
        "answerSelected":-1
      },
      {
        "options":[
          "Narendra",
          "Justin",
          "Scott",
          "Mahesh"
        ],
        "questionImg":null,
        "questionId":5,
        "question":"Who?",
        "answer":2,
        "answerSelected":-1
      },
      {
        "options":[
          "Justin",
          "Narendra",
          "Scott",
          "Mahesh"
        ],
        "questionImg":null,
        "questionId":6,
        "question":"Who?",
        "answer":2,
        "answerSelected":-1
      },
      {
        "options":[
          "Scott",
          "Justin",
          "Narendra",
          "Mahesh"
        ],
        "questionImg":null,
        "questionId":7,
        "question":"Who?",
        "answer":0,
        "answerSelected":-1
      },
      {
        "options":[
          "Narendra",
          "Justin",
          "Scott",
          "Mahesh"
        ],
        "questionImg":null,
        "questionId":8,
        "question":"Who?",
        "answer":2,
        "answerSelected":-1
      },
      {
        "options":[
          "Narendra",
          "Justin",
          "Scott",
          "Mahesh"
        ],
        "questionImg":null,
        "questionId":9,
        "question":"Who?",
        "answer":2,
        "answerSelected":-1
      }

    ]
  }
}
